Divyajitsinh Mahida

STUDENT/ASSISTANT GENERAL MANAGER

13712 Saint Michael Dr Little Rock, AR, 72211

(501) 413 4849

Dpmahida@ualr.edu

OBJECTIVE

To enhance my educational strength, to practice my knowledge, to display my management & technical skills, and to learn & grow as a competitive employee. I have Experience in different programming languages. I have done serval projects in different computer languages.

EDUCATION -

UA Little Rock (Fall 2018 – Spring 2022) Major: Information Science Minor: Business Information

System GPA: 3.5

Marketing

Central High School (Fall 2014 – Spring 2018) Honor graduate GPA: 3.75

KEY SKILLS -

Project Management
Budget Planning
Social Media
Planning
C++, HTML, JAVA
SQL Language
Applied networking
Computer system
CSS
Linux

EXPERIENCE

September 13, 2019 – Current
Assistant Manager • Front Desk • KNB Lodging

Guest Service Representative:

create guest reservation, help client check-in, making sure a comfortable stay, assigning duties to housekeepers, receive incoming calls, Brief information about property

I have experience in working with HTML, CSS, C++, Java, and JavaScript. I have done serval projects using those computer languages, I have knowledge about Database concepts and data mining.

ACHIEVEMENT

Trojan Pathway Scholarship
EIT Success Scholarship
Arkansas Lottery Scholarship
Dean's List (Spring 2020 – present)
Principle's Choice Award (2017)
Multiple Awards – Man of the Match – Arkansas Cricket Association

LEADERSHIP

National Honor Society (2014 - 2018)

National Honor Beta Club (2015 - 2018)

National Honor Collegiate

Scholars (2019 – Present)

National Society of Leadership and Success (2019 – Present)